Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
- IULIA (International Union of Life Insurance Agents), Publication (Box 546, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: International constitution and by-laws, 1977; Publication (Box 546, Folder 4)
- ILCA (International Labor Communications Association), Publication (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1990; Publication (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: FYI: Articles of interest to Labor Communicators - May 1995, Publication (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Correspondence: Enclosed is another set of camera ready slicks and FYI, which we hope you find useful, 1993; Publication (Box 546, Folder 5)
- ILCA (International Labor Communications Association), Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: ILCA journalistic awards contest, 1988; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: ILCA journalistic awards contest, 1991; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: ILCA journalistic awards contest, 1992; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Correspondence: You are cordially invited to attend the International Labor communications Association's Traditional Changing of the Guard Luncheon, 1989; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: correspondence: The judges for the ILCA's 1993 journalism contest are hard at work, Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Official Call, 1989; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1989 Constitutional Convention
  - Item 7: Official Call, 1991; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1991 Constitutional Convention
  - Item 8: FYI: May 1994, Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: ILCA Reporter, 1984; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: ILCA Reporter, 1989; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
    Notes: Aug/Sept 1989.
  - Item 11: ILCA Reporter, 1991; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
    Notes: Feb 1991.
  - Item 12: Political mailings - election '88, 1988; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Code of ethics, Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Advice to editors: stay neutral - by Don Dalena, 1988; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Union overnight courier services, 1989; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: New rates, new concepts, new words, but same old language problems, 1991; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: The labor paper racket, 1990; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: The labor paper racket, 1990; Publication (Box 546, Folder 6)
- Committee of Interns and Residents (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 546, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Calender book, 1983; Publication (Box 546, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Calender book, 1984; Publication (Box 546, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Newsletter -- Housestaff unions call for National Federation, 1984; Publication (Box 546, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Newsletter -- Housestaff unions call for National Federation, 1984; Publication (Box 546, Folder 7)
- Committee of Interns and Residents (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 546, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: By-laws and constitution of the, 1979; Publication (Box 546, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Executed contract: Interns and Residents., 1976; Publication (Box 546, Folder 8)
- Committee of Interns and Residents (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Health Care News - June 6-19, 1979, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Health Care News - June 6-19, 1979, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: PNHA backs federalized health plan, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Dear Kingsbrook House Staff Officer: Attached to this letter is a copy of the contract in effect between the Committee of Interns and Residents, 1979; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Appeal from the US District Court for the District of Columbia, 1979; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: How to recognize 10,000, 1979; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Wall Street Journal - articles from April 17, 1975, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
    Author: Wall Street Journal
  - Item 8: CIR bulletin - Special - Supreme Court: go to Congress, Congressional committee, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Official Call. 1981 Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: ILPA Convention, November 12-14, New York Sheraton Hotel, 1991; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Industrial relations face hard challenges in the eighties, says ILO Director-General, 1981; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: CIR Bulletin, 1976; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1976:Jan.)
  - Item 13: CIR Bulletin, 1979; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1979:Jan./Mar.)
  - Item 14: Misericordia Hospital Medical Center and Committee of Interns and Residents and New York State Nurses Association, 1979; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Foreign medical graduates in graduate medical education programs in New York City hospitals, May, 1979, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
    Author: Irving J. Lewis
  - Item 16: Milbank Memorial Fund quarterly/Health and Society - vol. 56, no. 4, 1978, Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
    Author: Robert G. Harmon
  - Item 17: Agreement College of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey and the Housestaff Organization of the College of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey/Committee of Interns and Residents: July 1, 1979 - June 30, 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Report of AFL-CIO delegation to Northern Ireland and to the Republic of Ireland, 1983; Publication (Box 546, Folder 9)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Publication (Box 546, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: By-laws of Local Union No. 377, 1984; Publication (Box 546, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: This agreement is made and entered into this 1st day of June, 1972Building Trades Employers Division of the Associated Building Contractors of the Triple Cities, Inc.(typewritten copy), Publication (Box 546, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: 1973-1976 Ironworkers' agreement (Box 546, Folder 10)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Publication (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Agreement, Iron Worker Employers, State of California and a portion of Nevada...and District Council of Iron Workers of the State of California and Vicinity...: July 1, 1986 - June 30, 1989, 1986-1989 (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Agreement, Iron Worker Employers, State of California and a portion of Nevada...and District Council of Iron Workers of the State of California and Vicinity...: July 1, 1989 - June 30, 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Agreement between National Steel and Shipbuilding Company and Shopmen's Local 627 of the International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers: October 1, 1984 - September 30, 1987, 1984-1987 (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Allied Building Metal Industries and Shopmen's Local Union, Local No. 455 of the International Association of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: Effective date July 1, 1973, Publication (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Hudson Valley Construction, Employers Association, Inc., Master Builders Association of Dutchess County, Inc., Contractors and Suppliers Association of Rockland County, Inc., Fabricators and Erectors Association and Local Union No. 417, Publication (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: California Ironworkers Field Pension trust: as amended through June 1, 1992, Publication (Box 546, Folder 11)
- Ironworkers Local 316 (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 547, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The History of Ironworkers Local 361: structural riggers, machinery movers & crectors (AFL-CIO)., 1990; Publication (Box 547, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The History of Ironworkers Local 361: structural riggers, machinery movers & crectors (AFL-CIO)., 1990; Publication (Box 547, Folder 1)
- International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Publication (Box 547, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1986; Publication (Box 547, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 547, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 547, Folder 2)
- Procter and Gamble Company; Ivorydale and St. Bernard Employees' Representation Association, Publication (Box 547, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Working agreement between Ivorydale and St. Bernard Employees' Representation Association and the Procter & Gamble Company: 1976-1979 (Box 547, Folder 3)
- Labor Party Advocates of America, Publication (Box 547, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Party Advocates: questions and answers, 1993; Publication (Box 547, Folder 4)
- Labor's Community Service Agency, Publication (Box 547, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Should unions be concernedabout smoking at work? You bet!, Publication (Box 547, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Laws mandating tobacco control: considerations of organized labor, Publication (Box 547, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Unions working together towards a tobacco-free 2000: implications and innovations, 1993; Publication (Box 547, Folder 5)
- Laborers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 1982-1984 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: National Postal agreement of 1973, Publication (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: United States Post Office, Elmira, NY Memorandum of Understanding, 1985; Publication (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Memorandum of understanding - United States Post Office, Elmira, NY, 1978; Publication (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Building and Construction agreement Laborers District Council, Westchester and Putnam Counties, N.Y. and the Building Trades Employers Association, Inc. and Builders Institute of Westchester and Putnam Counties, Inc.: 1973-1976 (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Local Union No. 435, Laborers International Union of North America and Construction Employers Labor Relations Association of New York State, Inc.: May 1, 1973 to May 31, 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Agreement made by and between Laborer's International Union of North America, Local No. 91, A.F. of L.-C.I.O. and the Building Industry Employers Association of Niagara County, New York, Inc.: 1976-1978 (Box 547, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Laborers' working agreement between the Eastern New York Construction Employers, Inc. and the Construction and General Laborers' Local Union No. 190, Albany, N.Y. and Vicinity: June 18, 1973, through May 31, 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 547, Folder 6)
- Laborers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 547, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1986; Publication (Box 547, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 547, Folder 7)
- National Post Office Mail Handlers, Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Mailhandler, 1978; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.9 (1978:Sep.)
  - Item 2: Mail Handler News Bulletin, 1985; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Mail Handlers Benefit Plan, 1978; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Mail Handlers Benefit Plan, 1979; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: We're the hidden heroes of the postal service, 1990; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: We're the hidden heroes of the postal service, 1990; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The Mail handlers Story: past and present achievements of a dynamic union, 1972; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: The Mail handlers Story: past and present achievements of a dynamic union, 1976; Publication (Box 547, Folder 8)
- Laundry, Dry Cleaning, and Dye House Workers' International Union, Publication (Box 547, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws - May 7, 1975, Publication (Box 547, Folder 10)
- League for Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 547, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A hidden agenda: the National Right to Work Committee and its campaign to undermine American trade unions, 1986; Publication (Box 547, Folder 11)
    Author: Karin Chenoweth
  - Item 2: Committee of Scholars and Artists for Polish Democacy, 1981; Publication (Box 547, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: In defense of Leonid Siry, Publication (Box 547, Folder 11)
- International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers' Union, Publication (Box 547, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1972; Publication (Box 547, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1972; Publication (Box 547, Folder 12)
- Leather Workers International Union, Publication (Box 547, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1977; Publication (Box 547, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1977; Publication (Box 547, Folder 13)
- National Rural Letter Carriers' Association, Publication (Box 548, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The National Rural Letter Carrier, 1981; Publication (Box 548, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.80:no.30 (1981:Aug. 8)
  - Item 2: Agreement between United States Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union, AFL-CIO, National Association of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO, National Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers and Group Leaders Division of the Laborers' International, 1975-1978 (Box 548, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between United States Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union, AFL-CIO, National Association of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO, National Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers and Group Leaders Division of the Laborers' International, 1975-1978 (Box 548, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement between National Association of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO and U.S. Postal Service: 1990-1994 (Box 548, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Proposed National Agreement.(photo copy), 1981-1984 (Box 548, Folder 1)
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 548, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New hand on the wheel, 1977; Publication (Box 548, Folder 2)
    Author: J. Joseph Vacca
  - Item 2: An affectionate farewell, 1968; Publication (Box 548, Folder 2)
    Author: Jerome J. Keating
  - Item 3: Meet your new President -, 1968; Publication (Box 548, Folder 2)
    Author: James H. Rademacher
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Capitol Notes, 1980; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Author: National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1980:Feb.)
  - Item 2: Capitol Notes, 1980; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 [Issue no.3] (1980:May)
  - Item 3: Capitol Notes, 1980; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 [Issue no.3] (1980:Aug.)
  - Item 4: Capitol Notes, 1980; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 [Issue no.4] (1980:Nov.)
  - Item 5: Capitol Notes, 1981; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 [Issue no.1] (1981:Feb.)
  - Item 6: Capitol Notes, 1981; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 [Issue no.3] (1981:Aug.)
  - Item 7: Capitol Notes, 1982; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 [Issue no.1] (1982:Feb.)
  - Item 8: Capitol Notes, 1982; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 [Issue no.2] (1982:May)
  - Item 9: Capitol Notes, 1982; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 [Issue no.4] (1982:Nov.)
  - Item 10: Capitol Notes, 1983; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 [Issue no.1] (1983:Feb.)
  - Item 11: Capitol Notes, 1983; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 [Issue no.5] (1983:May)
  - Item 12: Capitol Notes, 1983; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 [Issue no.6] (1983:Aug.)
  - Item 13: Capitol Notes, 1983; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 [Issue no.4] (1983:Nov.)
  - Item 14: Capitol Notes, 1984; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 [Issue no.1] (1984:Feb.)
  - Item 15: Capitol Notes, 1984; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 [Issue no.1] (1984:Feb.). Copy 2.
  - Item 16: Capitol Notes, 1984; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 [Issue no.2] (1984:May)
  - Item 17: Capitol Notes, 1984; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1984:Aug.)
  - Item 18: Capitol Notes, 1984; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 [Issue no.4] (1984:Nov.)
  - Item 19: Capitol Notes, 1984; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 [Issue no.4] (1984:Nov.). Copy 2.
  - Item 20: Postmark Washington, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1987:Spring)
  - Item 21: Postmark Washington, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1987:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 22: Postmark Washington, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1987:Summer)
  - Item 23: Postmark Washington, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1987:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 24: Postmark Washington, 1988; Publication (Box 548, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no. 1 (1988:Winter)
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 548, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 548, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 548, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Delivering your message to Congress: a lobbying guide for the Active Legislative Volunteer, 1981; Publication (Box 548, Folder 4)
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: NALC Retiree, 1984; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1984)
  - Item 2: So you want to carry the mail!, Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: So you want to carry the mail!, Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: If you are a Letter Carrier you can't afford not to be a member of the .., 1977; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: If you are a Letter Carrier you can't afford not to be a member of the .., 1977; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Letter Carriers and their union, Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph Smolen
  - Item 7: Postmark Washington, 1985; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1985:Winter)
  - Item 8: Postmark Washington, 1985; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1985:Spring)
  - Item 9: Postmark Washington, 1985; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1985:Summer)
  - Item 10: Postmark Washington, 1985; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1985:Fall)
  - Item 11: Postmark Washington, 1985; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1985:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 12: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1986:Winter)
  - Item 13: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1986:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 14: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1986:Spring)
  - Item 15: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1986:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 16: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1986:Summer)
  - Item 17: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1986:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 18: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1986:Fall)
  - Item 19: Postmark Washington, 1986; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1986:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 20: Postmark Washington, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1987:Winter)
  - Item 21: Postmark Washington, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1987:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 22: Postmark Washington, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Joint Bargaining Committee. Bulletin, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.1 (1987:Apr. 24)
  - Item 24: Joint Bargaining Committee. Bulletin, 1987; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.7 (1987"July 14)
  - Item 25: Bulletin From the National Association of Letter Carriers, 1988; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.4 (1988:Feb. 26)
  - Item 26: Bulletin From the National Association of Letter Carriers, 1988; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.5 (1988:Mar. 11)
  - Item 27: Bulletin From the National Association of Letter Carriers, 1988; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.5 (1988:Mar. 18)
  - Item 28: Responding to the threat of privatization, 1988; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: Fact sheet for NALC officers and stewarts
  - Item 29: The Letter Carriers and their union, Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
  - Item 30: The Letter Carriers and their union, Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Notes: Copy 3.
  - Item 31: Carriers in a common cause: a history of letter carriers and the NALC, 1989; Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Author: M. Brady Mikusko
  - Item 32: Open letter to the Professional Letter Carriers, Publication (Box 548, Folder 5)
    Author: William T. Sullivan
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 548, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The National Rural Letter Carrier, 1981; Publication (Box 548, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.80:no.30 (1981:Aug. 8). Copy 2.
  - Item 2: National agreement National Rural Letter Carriers' Association, United States Postal Service: 1984-1988 (Box 548, Folder 6)
    Notes: Published in The National Rural Letter Carrier. Photocopy.
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1994; Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
    Author: National Rural Letter Carriers' Association
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws, 1995; Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Constitution and by-laws, 1995; Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Save Six-Day Delivery ---, 1977; Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
    Author: Lester F. Miller
  - Item 5: Official Program 77th Annual Convention, 1977; Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Rural Carrier Benefit Plan, 1978; Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
    Author: Bureau of Retirement, Insurance, and Occupational Health
  - Item 7: A history of progress, Publication (Box 548, Folder 7)
- Librarians Association of the University of Washngton, Publication (Box 548, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Association of Librarians of the University of Washington, 1973; Publication (Box 548, Folder 8)
    Author: Librarians Association of the University of Washngton
  - Item 2: Association of Librarians of the University of Washington, 1973; Publication (Box 548, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Publication (Box 548, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A tradition of craftsmanship, 1966; Publication (Box 548, Folder 9)
    Author: Amalgamated Lithographers of America
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 549, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1986; Publication (Box 549, Folder 1)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws, 1991; Publication (Box 549, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Employee training needs of the railroad industry union perspectives: an address delivered to: Federal Railroad Administration Conference, 1978; Publication (Box 549, Folder 1)
    Author: L.S. Loomis
    Notes: Address delivered to the Federal Railroad Administration Conference
  - Item 4: Agreement dated March 6, 1975 between railroads represented by the National Carriers' Conference Committee and employees of such railroads represented by the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 549, Folder 1)
    Author: National Carriers' Conference Committee; BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 549, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Due process: a manual for use in providing representation to employees involved in discipline and dismissal cases, 1978; Publication (Box 549, Folder 2)